Finding aid to the Classes of 1879-1890 records CA.MS.01023
Smith College Archives
Classes of 1879-1890 records
1844-2003
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Class of 1880.
CA.MS.01023
49.667 linear feet (96 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Whenever donation information for a particular set of material is known, it is included in the finding aid below. However, a majority of the material was not formally accessioned and its origins are not currently known.
Arrangement
This collection brings together twelve record groups that are arranged chronologically, one per graduating class. However, since some materials are placed in a class record group based on when they were created, and not by whom, materials relelvant to a class may exist in more than one series.
Related Materials
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes. These files, which are organized by class and are housed in the boxes numbered immnediately after each set of Class Records are not currently listed in any finding aid; contact Special Collections for more information.
Scope and Contents
The Classes of 1879-1890 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Smith College -- Students; Smith College--Alumni and alumnae; Smith College. Class of 1879.; Smith College. Class of 1881.; Smith College. Class of 1882.; Smith College. Class of 1883.; Smith College. Class of 1884.; Smith College. Class of 1885.; Smith College. Class of 1886.; Smith College. Class of 1887.; Smith College. Class of 1888.; Smith College. Class of 1889.; Smith College. Class of 1890.; Smith College--Alumni and alumnae; Smith College--Students.
- Class of 1879 Records, 1844-1984; 6 boxes (5 linear feet)
  Biographical / Historical
  The Class of 1879 was the first graduating class of Smith College.
  Scope and Contents
  The Class of 1879 Records contain materials describing the history of the students of the first graduating class of Smith College. Types of materials include black and white photographs, programs, magazine and newspaper articles, lists of students, letters, correspondence, and information about the Class of 1879's commencement and reunions.
  - Class of 1879: Commencement (Box 1380, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1879: Baccalaureate (Box 1380, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1879: Chronology, 1875-1879 (Box 1380, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1879: Clippings (Box 1380, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1879: Commencement Music (Box 1380, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1879: Concert and Reception, 1878 (Box 1380, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1879: Group Photos (Box 1380, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1879: History, 1876-77; 1932; 1934; 1938 (Box 1380, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1879: Reunions (1925) (Box 1380, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1879: Reunions (1929) (Box 1380, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1879: Reunions (Photographs), 1929 (Box 1380, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1879: Senior Reception (Box 1380, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1879: Sophomore Reception to 1880, 1877 (Box 1380, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1879: Subjects for Essays (Box 1380, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1879: Adkins, Mary (Correspondence), 1930; 1937-39; 1940-41; 1965 (Box 1380, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1879: Adkins, Mary (Photographs), 1934 (Box 1380, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1879: Bonney, Mary Herrick (Photographs) (Box 1380, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1879: Carleton, Abbie Harriet (Correspondence), 1929 (Box 1380, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1879: Cushing, Eleanor Philbrook (Box 1380, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1879: Edwards, Adelaide Frances Dyer (Photographs) (Box 1380, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1879: Gorham, Mary Etta (Box 1380, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1879: Gulliver, Julia Henrietta, 1910; 1912-14; 1915; 1917 (Box 1380, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1879: Leonard, Henrietta, 1897; 1938 (Box 1380, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Box 1380, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (General), 1875-86; 1900; 1904; 1909-10; 1913 (Box 1382, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Manuscripts, Typescripts, etc.), undated (Box 1382, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Ph.D. Degree), 1881-82; 1917; 1956; 1961; 1983-84 (Box 1382, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Photo Album), undated (Box 1382, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Morris Family History), undated (Box 1382, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Photographs), 1875-76; 1896; 1968-69 (Box 1382, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Publications), 1884; 1896; 1898-99; 1901-06; 1915; 1924 (Box 1382, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Twigs From a Family Tree), 1936 (Box 1382, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (A Valley Family by Alice Cone Perry), undated (Box 1382, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Correspondence with Ellen W. Clarke), 1875-1879 (Box 1383, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Correspondence with Ellen W. Clarke), 1876-1884 (Box 1383, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Correspondence with Charles Cone), 1882-83; 1895; 1897 (Box 1383, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Correspondence with Family), 1844; 1867; 1896; 1901; 1905; 1911 (Box 1383, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Correspondence- General), 1880-82; 1929 (Box 1383, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Correspondence- General), 1883; 1902-03; 1909; 1913; 1924-25; 1927-29 (Box 1383, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Correspondence with Almira N. Morris), 1871-1879 (Box 1383, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Correspondence with Almira N. Morris), 1880-1893 (Box 1383, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Correspondence with Alice Perry (Cone)), 1897; 1904-06; 1929; 1938-41; 1958 (Box 1383, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Correspondence with L. Clark Seelye), 1903; 1914; 1916; 1920; 1922 (Box 1383, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Journal), 1883-1887 (Box 1384, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Journal), 1887 (Box 1384, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Journal), 1893-1895 (Box 1384, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Journal), 1896-1899 (Box 1384, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Journal), 1900-1908 (Box 1384, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1879: Morris, Kate E. (Journal), 1909-1929 (Box 1384, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1879: Osborne, Alice Cook, 1929 (Box 1380, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1879: Palmer, Anna Louise (Box 1380, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1879: Spaulding, Sylvia Sanders, 1918-1920 (Box 1380, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1879: Taber, Sarah (Box 1380, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1879: Tuckerman, Corinne Marie, 1875; 1929; 1931; 1938-39 (Box 1380, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1879: Warner, Harriet Blanche, 1870-71; 1875; 1880; 1925; 1929; 1930-32 (Box 1381, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1879: Warner, Harriet Blanche (Correspondence with Charles S. Palmer), 1930; 1932-41 (Box 1381, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1879: Warner, Harriet Blanche (First Days at Smith College), 1923 (Box 1381, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1879: Warner, Harriet Blanche (Lithography / Photographs), 1923; 1926 (Box 1381, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1879: Warner, Harriet Blanche (Lecture Notes / Physics), 1878 (Box 1381, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1879: Warner, Harriet Blanche (Lecture Notes), 1876-78 (Box 1381, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1879: Warner, Harriet Blanche (Course Notes), undated (Box 1381, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1879: Warner, Harriet Blanche (Photograph Album), undated (Box 1384.1)
  - Class of 1879: Whiton, Mary Bartlett (Correspondence), 1883; 1906; 1924; 1929; 1930-31; 1933-39 (Box 1381, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1879: Whiton, Mary Bartlett (Photographs), 1888-89; 1896; 1934; 1937 (Box 1381, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1879: Whiton, Mary Bartlett (Scrapbook), Late 1800s-Early 1900s (Box 1381, Folder 10)
- Class of 1880 Records, 1877-1949; 1 boxes (5 linear inches)
  The Class of 1880 was the second graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1880 Records contain materials describing the history of the students of the Class of 1880. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, correspondence, programs, invitations, songs, and other information about the graduation and reunions of the Class of 1880.
  - Class of 1880: Commencement (Box 1380, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1880: Commencement Speaker (Box 1380, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1880: Commencement Music (Box 1380, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1880: Songs (Box 1380, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1880: Group Photographs (Box 1380, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1880: Poetry (Box 1380, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1880: Reunions, undated (Box 1380, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1880: Reunions, 1905 (Box 1380, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1880: Reunions, 1910 (Box 1380, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1880: Reunions, 1925 (Box 1380, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1880: Reunions, 1930 (Box 1380, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1880: Reunions, 1935 (Box 1380, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1880: Reunions, 1940 (Box 1380, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1880: Bisbee, Anna Bartlett (Box 1380, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1880: Bisbee, Mary Otis (Box 1380, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1880: Clark, Josephine Adelaide (Box 1380, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1880: Devoll, Ida Eugenia, 1930-34; 1936 (Box 1380, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1880: Eaton, Ella Elizabeth (Box 1380, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1880: Gorham, Anna Kellogg (Box 1380, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1880: Locke, Mary Stoughton (Box 1380, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1880: Locke, Mary Stoughton (Correspondence), 1900; 1930-34; 1936-38; 1940; 1945; 1949 (Box 1380, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1880: Miller, Helen Lyman (Correspondence: Sept.-Nov.), 1877 (Box 1380, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1880: Miller, Helen Lyman (Correspondence: Dec.-Feb.), 1877-1878 (Box 1380, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1880: Miller, Helen Lyman (Correspondence: Mar.-Apr.), 1878 (Box 1380, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1880: Miller, Helen Lyman (Correspondence: May-June), 1878 (Box 1380, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1880: Miller, Helen Lyman (Photographs) (Box 1380, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1880: Robinson, Jennie Justina (Box 1380, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1880: Seymour, May (Box 1380, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1880: Tate, Emma (Correspondence), 1930-34; 1936-38; 1941 (Box 1380, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1880: Tate, Emma (Photographs) (Box 1380, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1880: Tuckerman, Lillian Ellinwood (Box 1380, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1880: Toxbury, Helen (Correspondence), 1900; 1906; 1930-34; 1936-37 (Box 1380, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1880: Toxbury, Helen (Photographs) (Box 1380, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1880: Wetherbee, Netta Elizabeth (Correspondence), 1881; 1884-85; 1887; 1889-1910; 1912; 1914-16; 1918-25; 1927-32; 1934; 1936-38; 1940 (Box 1380, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1880: Wetherbee, Netta Elizabeth (Photographs) (Box 1380, Folder 35)
  - Box missing since Feb. 1999 (Box 1386)
- Class of 1881 Records, 1876-1998; 5 boxes (2 linear feet)
  The Class of 1881 was the third graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1881 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1881. Types of materials include black and white photographs, class letters, publications, correspondence, newspaper clippings, scrapbooks, photo albums, and student's class notes, as well as information regarding the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1881.
  - Class of 1881: Class Letters, 1883; 1893; 1895-97; 1899; 1900; 1902; 1914-16; 1939-41; 1945-46 (Box 1387, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1881: Clippings, undated (Box 1387, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1881: Commencement (Box 1387, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1881: Commencement Music (Box 1387, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1881: Germans, 1880-81 (Box 1387, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1881: Group Photos (Box 1387, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1881: Official Circular (Box 1387, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1881: Organization, 1880-81; 1887 (Box 1387, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1881: Publications, 1888-89; 1891; 1894-95; 1897; 1899; 1904-05 (Box 1387, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1881: Reunions, 1887; 1889; 1915-16; 1937; 1941; 1945-46 (Box 1387, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1881: Reunion Photographs, 1931; 1941 (Box 1387, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1881: Arms, Harriet Elizabeth (Box 1388, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1881: Barnard, Mary A. (Box 1388, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1881: Browne, Sarah Alice, 1887; 1906; 1912-15; 1928; 1979 (Box 1388, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1881: Bryant, Martha, 1918-19 (Box 1388, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1881: Cartwright, Annie, 1919 (Box 1388, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1881: Cheever, Charlotte Barrell (Box 1388, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1881: Clapp, Lucia Maria (Box 1388, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1881: Clapp, Lucia Maria, 1881 (Scrapbook / Photo Album), 1877-1881 (Box 1389.1)
  - Class of 1881: Clarke, Rachel, 1934 (Box 1388, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1881: Cunningham, Marion Hobart (Box 1388, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1881: Dibble, Mary (Box 1388, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1881: Dibble, Mary Frances (Album), undated (Box 1390)
  - Class of 1881: Dunton, Harriette Mandana, 1918-19 (Box 1388, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1881: Dunton, Harriette Mandana (Class notes, Religion and Literature), undated (Box 1388, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1881: Dunton, Harriette Mandana (Notebook "Essays"), undated (Box 1388, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1881: Ensign, Mary Louise, 1905 (Box 1388, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1881: Fosdick, Lucy (Box 1388, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1881: Fosdick, Sarah (Box 1388, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1881: Gill, Laura Drake, 1888; 1902; 1909; 1913; 1918; 1925 (Box 1388, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1881: Gill, Laura Drake (The Cosmopolitan, "Women as College Presidents"), 1902 (Box 1388, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1881: Gray, Emma C.B. (Box 1388, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1881: Guyer, Caroline (Box 1388, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1881: Haven, Laura Belle, 1879-81; 1883; 1920; 1961 (Box 1388, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1881: Heard, Sarah (Box 1388, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1881: Hoyt, Anna Marilla, 1883-84; 1914-15 (Box 1388, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1881: Hoyt, Anna Marilla (Photographs) (Box 1388, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1881: Huntington, Eliza Prentiss (Box 1388, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1881: Huntington, Eliza Prentiss (Correspondence), 1899; 1900; 1906; 1916; 1931; 1933; 1938; 1941; 1945 (Box 1391, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1881: Huntington, Eliza Prentiss (Material on her Old Age), 1923; 1929; 1933-34; 1954; 1956-57; 1959; 1998 (Box 1391, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1881: Huntington, Eliza Prentiss (Photographs), 1909; 1940; 1952; 1956-57 (Box 1391, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1881: Huntington, Eliza Prentiss (Round Robin), 1917-18; 1920; 1922-23; 1926; 1930-45 (Box 1391, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1881: Huntington, Eliza Prentiss (Secretary of Class Papers), 1915-28; 1936-38 (Box 1391, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1881: Huntington, Eliza Prentiss (Scrapbook / Photo Album), 1881-1936 (Box 1391, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1881: Huntington, Eliza Prentiss (Scrapbook), 1878-82 (Box 1391)
  - Class of 1881: Joel, Julia M., 1920; 1936; 1981 (Box 1388, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1881: Kellogg, Sarah Delano (General) (Box 1389, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1881: Kellogg, Sarah Delano (Letters), 1920; 1923; 1929-31; 1934-35; 1938-41 (Box 1389, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1881: King, Effie (Box 1389, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1881: Lathe, Agnes (Box 1389, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1881: Leonard, Mary Adeline, undated (Box 1389, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1881: Lewis, Frances, 1888 (Box 1389, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1881: Miner, Affa S. (Lecture Notes), 1878-81 (Box 1389, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1881: Miner, Affa S. (Letters), 1876-77; 1879; 1919-20; 1931 (Box 1389, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1881: Miner, Affa S. (Photographs), 1893 (Box 1389, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1881: Nettleton, Mary Eliza, 1956 (Box 1389, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1881: Owen, Amelia (Box 1389, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1881: Pearson, Helen (Box 1389, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1881: Pratt, Harriet, 1883; 1890 (Box 1389, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1881: Proctor, Mary, 1880-81; 1905; 1918; 1928; 1930 (Box 1389, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1881: Saunderson, Laura Maria (Correspondence re: M.A.), 1885 (Box 1389, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1881: Saunderson, Laura Maria (Photographs), 1888 (Box 1389, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1881: Seymour, Clara (Box 1389, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1881: Taylor, Isabelle (Correspondence), 1916; 1931 (Box 1389, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1881: Taylor, Isabelle (Photographs) (Box 1389, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1881: Tyler, Mary E., 1917; 1919; 1931 (Box 1389, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1881: Warner, Harriet Blanche, undated (Box 1389, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1881: Willmer, Amy, 1883; 1919; 1931 (Box 1389, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1881: Unidentified Album, 1877-1883 (Box 1390.1)
- Class of 1882 Records, 1879-2000; 7 boxes (2 linear feet)
  The Class of 1882 was the fourth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1882 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1882. Types of materials include letters, correspondence, black and white photographs, scrapbooks, student notes, and materials from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1882.
  - Class of 1882: Class Essay (Box 1392, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1882: Class Letters, 1913; 1925 (Box 1392, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1882: Class Officers (Correspondence and Finances), 1908-10; 1912; 1922 (Box 1392, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1882: Class Supper (Box 1392, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1882: Commencement Poems (Box 1392, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1882: Commencement (Box 1392, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1882: Commencement Music (Box 1392, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1882: Commencement Speaker, 1881-82 (Box 1392, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1882: Group Photos (Box 1392, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1882: History, 1879; undated (Box 1392, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1882: Photographer Records (Box 1392, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1882: Records, 1878-1882 (Box 1392, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1882: Reunions (1889) (Box 1392, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1882: Reunions (1907) (Box 1392, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1882: Reunions (1910) (Box 1392, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1882: Reunions (1912) (Box 1392, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1882: Reunions (1917) (Box 1392, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1882: Reunions (1922) (Box 1392, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1882: Reunions (1927) (Box 1392, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1882: Reunions (1932) (Box 1392, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1882: Reunions (1942) (Box 1392, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1882: Senior Reception (Box 1392, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1882: Songs (Box 1392, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1882: Sophomore Reception, 1879 (Box 1392, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1882: Statistics, undated (Box 1392, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1882: Alden, Mary Elizabeth (Box 1393, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1882: Allen, Annie Elizabeth (Box 1393, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1882: Ayres, Edith Jane (Box 1393, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1882: Blake, Isabel (Correspondence, Jan-Mar), 1878 (Box 1393, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1882: Blake, Isabel (Correspondence, Sept-Oct), 1878 (Box 1393, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1882: Blake, Isabel (Correspondence, Nov-Dec), 1878 (Box 1393, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1882: Blake, Isabel (Correspondence, Jan-Mar), 1879 (Box 1393, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1882: Blake, Isabel (Letters), 1879-81; 1909-10 (Box 1393, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1882: Blake, Isabel (Photographs) (Box 1393, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1882: Blanchard, Grace, 1921; 1933-34 (Box 1393, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Box 1393, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Birth Record), 1859 (Box 1395, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Student Notes), undated (Box 1395, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Journal), 1876; 1879; 1880 (Box 1395, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Correspondence to Family: Jul, Sept, Jun, Oct), 1870-71; 1878 (Box 1395, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Correspondence to Family: Nov-Dec), 1878 (Box 1395, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Correspondence to Family: Jan-Feb), 1879 (Box 1395, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Correspondence to Family: Apr-Jun), 1879 (Box 1395, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Correspondence to Family: Jul-Dec), 1879 (Box 1395, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick and Frona Marie (1883): (Correspondence to Family: Jan-Mar), 1880 (Box 1395, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick and Frona Marie (1883): (Correspondence to Family: Apr-May), 1880 (Box 1395, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick and Frona Marie (1883): (Correspondence to Family: Sept-Mar), 1880-1881 (Box 1395, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick and Frona Marie (1883): (Correspondence to Family: Mar-Jun), 1881 (Box 1395, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick and Frona Marie (1883): (Correspondence to Family: Sept-Dec), 1881 (Box 1395, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick and Frona Marie (1883): (Correspondence to Family: Jan-Mar) (Box 1395, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick and Frona Marie (1883): (Correspondence to Family: Apr-Jun), 1882-1883 (Box 1395, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick and Frona Marie (1883): (Correspondence to Family: May), 1886 (Box 1395, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick and Frona Marie (1883): (Correspondence to Family), undated (Box 1395, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Photographs), 1921; 1932 (Box 1395, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Adams, Mrs.), 1888 (Box 1395, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Allen, Annie), 1918; 1926-26; 1928; 1930-32; 1934-37) (Box 1395, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Brooks, Elizabeth), 1930 (Box 1395, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Brooks, Harriet), 1910 (Box 1395, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Brooks, Ina), 1907 (Box 1395, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Browne, Nina), 1917; 1920; 1922; 1934-37 (Box 1395, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Clark, Mrs. Levi), 1880-82 (Box 1395, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Foster, Mrs.), 1880 (Box 1395, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Gulliver, Mary), 1913; 1920-21 (Box 1395, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Kittredge, Frances), undated (Box 1395, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Knapp, Elizabeth P.), 1926; 1935 (Box 1395, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Lowry, Anna), 1920-21 (Box 1395, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Oughterson, Mrs. W.A.), 1920 (Box 1395, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Sedgwick, Mary), undated (Box 1395, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Sill, E.R.), 1881-82 (Box 1395, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Letters: Smith, Mrs.), 1917 (Box 1395, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Scrapbook), Late1870s-Mid 1880s (Box 1396)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Scrapbook), Late1870s-Mid 1880s (Box 1396)
  - Class of 1882: Brooks, Esther Herrick (Scrapbook), Late1870s-Mid 1880s (Box 1396)
  - Class of 1882: Brown, Fanny Chamberlain (Box 1393, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1882: Browne, Nina Eliza (Box 1393, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1882: Cheever, Ellen Tyler, 1878-79 (Box 1393, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1882: Clark, Sophia Cook (Box 1393, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1882: Clarke, Mary Reynolds, 1959 (Box 1393, Folder 16)